42:export async function updateMyTeacherProfile(userId: string, data: any) {
83:export async function updateUserPassword(userId: string, newPassword: string) {
105:export async function login(formData: FormData) {
224:export async function getCurrentUser() {
260:export async function getParentStudents(parentId: string) {
293:export async function logout() {
312:export async function getUniqueUsername(baseUsername: string) {
358:export async function addStudent(formData: FormData, isSignup: boolean = false) {
572:export async function updateStudent(formData: FormData) {
815:export async function getStudentDetailsForEdit(userId: string, requestingTeacherId?: string) {
911:export async function getTeachersAndAcademies() {
956:export async function addCurriculum(formData: FormData) {
1025:export async function getMonthlyAttendance(studentId: string, startDateStr: string, endDateStr: string, teacherId?: string | null) {
1054:export async function getDailyAttendance(studentId: string, dateStr: string, sessionType: string = 'regular') {
1076:export async function saveDailyAttendance(attendanceData: any) {
1093:export async function saveAttendanceSessionAction(attendanceData: any) {
1159:export async function deleteAttendanceSessionAction(studentId: string, date: string, sessionType: string) {
1189:export async function deleteDailyAttendance(id: string) {
1210:export async function updateCurriculum(formData: FormData) {
1272:export async function saveTypingResult(data: {
1385:export async function getStudentGoals(studentId: string) {
1406:export async function addStudentGoal(studentId: string, title: string) {
1436:export async function toggleStudentGoal(studentId: string, goalIndex: number) {
1469:export async function deleteStudentGoal(studentId: string, goalIndex: number) {
1496:export async function getTypingRecords(studentId: string, daysBack: number = 90) {
1533:export async function getAttendanceRecords(studentId: string, year: number, month: number) {
1579:export async function uploadContentImage(file: File, section: string): Promise<{ success: boolean, url?: string, error?: string }> {
1659:export async function updateContent(formData: FormData) {
1754:export async function getContent() {
1774:export async function getMainCurriculums() {
1804:export async function updateMainCurriculums(curriculums: Array<{ id: string; display_order?: number }>) {
1846:export async function addMainCurriculum(formData: FormData) {
1916:export async function updateMainCurriculum(formData: FormData) {
1975:export async function deleteMainCurriculum(curriculumId: string) {
2010:export async function addTeacher(formData: FormData) {
2147:export async function updateTeacher(formData: FormData) {
2306:export async function getTeacherDetails(teacherId: string) {
2350:export async function toggleTeacherTuitionPermission(teacherId: string, canManage: boolean) {
2379:export async function updateAdminProfile(formData: FormData) {
2519:export async function saveConsultation(formData: FormData) {
2580:export async function getConsultations() {
2610:export async function getAdminDashboardData() {
2712:export async function updateConsultationStatus(formData: FormData) {
2766:export async function getInstructors() {
2833:export async function deleteStudent(studentId: string) {
2979:export async function createStudentSignupRequest(studentData: {
3096:export async function getNewStudentSignupRequests(teacherId?: string) {
3174:export async function approveNewStudentSignupRequest(requestId: string) {
3258:export async function rejectNewStudentSignupRequest(requestId: string, rejectionReason?: string) {
3335:export async function deleteTeacher(teacherId: string) {
3384:export async function updateTeacherLabelColor(teacherId: string, color: string) {
3412:export async function getStudentProgress(studentId: string) {
3442:export async function addStudentXP(studentId: string, amount: number, reason: string) {
3472:export async function updateStudentProgress(studentId: string, progressData: any) {
3562:export async function getCurriculums() {
3583:export async function createPortfolioEntry(
3665:export async function trackVisit(isUnique: boolean = false) {
